Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Your Highness
صاحب السمو
Wu Mao said the Wujia Village chief is a tough nut.
قال وو ماو إن رئيس قرية ووجيا رجل عنيد.
He keeps opposing us again and again.
إنه يواصل معارضتنا مراراً وتكراراً.
If that Shi Feifan kid is found by him,
إذا عثر عليه ذلك الطفل شي فيفان،
he'll definitely tell the truth.
سيقول الحقيقة بالتأكيد.
If that doesn't work,
إذا لم ينجح ذلك،
find a way to shut them all up.
ابحث عن طريقة لإسكاتهم جميعاً.
You understand all my orders, right?
أنت تفهم جميع أوامري، أليس كذلك؟
Understood.
مفهوم.
How could he be here?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هنا؟
No wonder she didn't eat it herself.
لا عجب أنها لم تأكله بنفسها.
Turns out it was for the chief.
اتضح أنها كانت للرئيس.
We really do need food.
نحن بحاجة ماسة إلى الطعام.
Thank you, everyone.
شكراً لكم جميعاً.
This poor child...
هذا الطفل المسكين...
Her father was beaten to death.
تعرض والدها للضرب حتى الموت.
Her mother was taken away.
أُخذت والدتها بعيداً.
Suffered that damn Your Highness's abuse.
لقد عانيت من إساءة سموكم اللعينة.
Out of shame and anger,
من الخزي والغضب،
she ran into a wall.
اصطدمت بالحائط.
This child is nine years old.
هذا الطفل يبلغ من العمر تسع سنوات.
She still won't speak.
ما زالت ترفض الكلام.
In this family,
في هذه العائلة،
just to have something to eat,
فقط لأحصل على شيء آكله،
they've sold everything they could.
لقد باعوا كل ما في وسعهم.
Stop for a moment.
توقف للحظة.
We're mainly here to ask you something.
نحن هنا بشكل أساسي لنسألك شيئاً.
I...
أنا...
I don't know anything.
لا أعرف شيئاً.
Wu Mao.
وو ماو.
He's at the chief's house.
إنه في منزل رئيس القبيلة.
Why are you alone?
لماذا أنت وحيد؟
I walk fast.
أمشي بسرعة.
Lord Nan said,
قال اللورد نان:
stir things up first.
أثيروا الأمور أولاً.
The main force will arrive soon.
ستصل القوة الرئيسية قريباً.
You old man...
يا رجل عجوز...
We gave you steamed buns.
قدمنا ​​لكم كعكات مطهوة على البخار.
How can you talk like that?
كيف يمكنك التحدث بهذه الطريقة؟
Don't talk about the chief like that.
لا تتحدث عن الرئيس بهذه الطريقة.
Stay out of grown-ups' business.
ابتعد عن شؤون الكبار.
Take her back.
خذها مرة أخرى.
Safe and sound.
سالماً معافى.
Young Duke.
الدوق الشاب.
This is the Imperial Sword bestowed by His Majesty.
هذا هو السيف الإمبراطوري الذي منحه جلالته.
Chief, you can trust us now, right?
يا رئيس، يمكنك الوثوق بنا الآن، أليس كذلك؟
My name is Shi Feifan.
اسمي شي فيفان.
My father is Duke of Nan, Shi Mengze.
والدي هو دوق نان، شي منغزي.
He leads the Shi Family Army,
هو قائد جيش عائلة شي،
defending our country as Duke of Nan.
الدفاع عن بلدنا بصفتي دوق نان.
Chief.
رئيس.
Please, get up, get up.
من فضلك، انهض، انهض.
There's finally hope.
أخيرًا، هناك أمل.
Don't kneel, please stand up.
لا تركعوا، من فضلكم قفوا.
Quick, quick, please rise.
بسرعة، بسرعة، من فضلك انهض.
There's hope now.
هناك أمل الآن.
I want to know the truth.
أريد أن أعرف الحقيقة.
Over there.
هناك.
Folks, hurry up.
يا جماعة، أسرعوا.
Safe and sound.
سالماً معافى.
I understand.
أفهم.
Everyone, everyone!
الجميع، الجميع!
Folks, it's him!
يا جماعة، إنه هو!
He's here to harm us.
إنه هنا ليؤذينا.
Grab him!
أمسك به!
Everyone, everyone!
الجميع، الجميع!
He's an important official from the capital.
إنه مسؤول مهم من العاصمة.
He's here to save us from disaster.
إنه هنا لينقذنا من الكارثة.
Chief, are you out of your mind?
يا رئيس، هل فقدت عقلك؟
Save us from disaster?
هل تنقذنا من الكارثة؟
An important official?
مسؤول مهم؟
What big official comes to a place like this?
أي مسؤول كبير يأتي إلى مكان كهذا؟
If you ask me,
إذا سألتني،
he just wants to win our trust
إنه يريد فقط أن يكسب ثقتنا
so he can steal our seed grain.
حتى يتمكن من سرقة حبوبنا.
If he steals our seed grain,
إذا سرق حبوبنا،
what will we eat?
ماذا سنأكل؟
How will we survive?
كيف سننجو؟
Right?
يمين؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Catch him!
أمسك به!
You people are clueless!
أنتم يا قوم جاهلون!
We came with the emperor's decree.
لقد جئنا بأمر من الإمبراطور.
What?
ماذا؟
The imperial decree?
المرسوم الإمبراطوري؟
He's just making it up.
إنه يختلق الأمر فحسب.
Then show us the decree!
ثم أرنا المرسوم!
Well, Young Duke...
حسناً، أيها الدوق الشاب...
Can't show it, can you?
لا يمكنك إظهار ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
He's a fraud!
إنه محتال!
Fraud!
احتيال!
Spy!
جاسوس!
Spy, you!
جاسوس أنت!
Fraud! Fraud!
احتيال! احتيال!
You all...
أنتم جميعاً...
Wu Mao, right?
وو ماو، صحيح؟
I think you're the real problem.
أعتقد أنك أنت المشكلة الحقيقية.
Speak up.
تكلم بصراحة.
Who's behind you?
من يقف خلفك؟
It's him!
إنه هو!
I've seen him several times
لقد رأيته عدة مرات
sneaking around for seed grain.
يتسلل للحصول على حبوب البذور.
He was just with a constable.
كان برفقة شرطي.
Wu Mao, you...
وو ماو، أنت...
No wonder the constable shows up whenever we collect grain.
لا عجب أن يظهر الشرطي كلما جمعنا الحبوب.
So you're the real spy!
إذن أنت الجاسوس الحقيقي!
Wu Mao, how dare you trick us!
وو ماو، كيف تجرؤ على خداعنا!
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
Lord Nan will be here soon.
سيصل اللورد نان قريباً.
He'll have you all arrested.
سيقوم باعتقالكم جميعاً.
The county jail is stricter than the Imperial Prison.
سجن المقاطعة أكثر صرامة من السجن الإمبراطوري.
You'll all be begging me then.
ستتوسلون إليّ جميعاً حينها.
Wu Mao, how could you side with bandits?
وو ماو، كيف يمكنك أن تقف إلى جانب قطاع الطرق؟
You old fool!
يا لك من أحمق عجوز!
Lord Nan is our county's magistrate.
اللورد نان هو قاضي مقاطعتنا.
He has support in the capital too.
ويحظى بدعم في العاصمة أيضاً.
If you know what's good for you,
إذا كنت تعرف ما هو الأفضل لك،
arrest them now.
ألقوا القبض عليهم الآن.
Then I might plead for you.
حينها قد أتوسل إليك.
Folks, grab him!
يا جماعة، أمسكوا به!
Yes, grab him! Grab him!
نعم، أمسك به! أمسك به!
Beat him! Beat him!
اهزمه! اهزمه!
Hit!
يضرب!
Go!
يذهب!
Stay close.
ابقَ على مقربة.
Young Duke, wake up!
أيها الدوق الصغير، استيقظ!
Young Duke, sir, be careful—it's a trap!
أيها الدوق الشاب، كن حذراً - إنه فخ!
Young Duke!
الدوق الشاب!
Wake up, Young Duke!
استيقظ يا دوق الصغير!
Kneel before me!
اركع أمامي!
Kneel!
اركع!
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Let them go.
دعهم يذهبون.
Fine.
بخير.
But...
لكن...
You have to hand over the Gatling.
عليك تسليم مدفع جاتلينج.
Tell me, where did you hide it?
أخبرني، أين أخفيته؟
I heard this weapon is powerful.
سمعت أن هذا السلاح قوي.
I'd like to try it myself.
أود أن أجرب ذلك بنفسي.
What are you planning?
ما هي خططك؟
Your Highness Liang Qing made such a big scene
أثار صاحب السمو ليانغ تشينغ ضجة كبيرة
just for this thing?
فقط من أجل هذا الشيء؟
This isn't much, really.
هذا ليس بالكثير، في الحقيقة.
It's just a hunk of iron that hurts your hand.
إنها مجرد قطعة من الحديد تؤذي يدك.
I advise you to let us go.
أنصحك بأن تدعنا نذهب.
Or you'll regret it.
وإلا ستندم على ذلك.
The emperor is far away.
الإمبراطور بعيد.
Do you believe it?
هل تصدق ذلك؟
I can have them killed one by one right in front of you.
بإمكاني أن أأمر بقتلهم واحداً تلو الآخر أمام عينيك مباشرة.
Then chop you up and feed you to the dogs.
ثم يقطعونك ويطعمونك للكلاب.
You—
أنت-
Our Young Duke
دوقنا الشاب
is here by imperial decree.
موجود هنا بموجب مرسوم إمبراطوري.
Don't do anything reckless.
لا تفعل أي شيء متهور.
You are the chicken—
أنت الدجاجة—
I am—
أنا أكون-
I—I—I...
أنا... أنا... أنا...
Sir,
سيد،
You are the fish, I am the knife.
أنت السمكة، وأنا السكين.
Go.
يذهب.
Since I'm the knife,
بما أنني السكين،
I can cut you down.
أستطيع أن أهزمك.
You—You...
أنتَ... أنتَ...
Our Duke of Nan won't let you off.
لن يتركك دوق نان تفلت من العقاب.
I'll burn Wujia Village to the ground.
سأحرق قرية ووجيا عن بكرة أبيها.
So no one can testify against me.
لذلك لا يستطيع أحد أن يشهد ضدي.
What can you do to us?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل بنا؟
You—
أنت-
On your turf,
على أرضك،
of course we follow your lead.
بالطبع سنتبع توجيهاتكم.
Since you know your place,
بما أنك تعرف مكانتك،
I'll make it quick for you later.
سأنجز الأمر بسرعة من أجلك لاحقاً.
Get them!
احصل عليهم!
I'm the Imperial Commissioner.
أنا المفوض الإمبراطوري.
Don't you think
ألا تعتقد ذلك؟
I'm missing something?
هل فاتني شيء ما؟
Tell me, where is the Imperial Sword?
أخبرني، أين السيف الإمبراطوري؟
The Imperial Sword is somewhere safe.
السيف الإمبراطوري موجود في مكان آمن.
If you want to know, let them go.
إذا كنت تريد أن تعرف، دعهم يذهبون.
You—You—You...
أنتَ - أنتَ - أنتَ...
Tell me right now!
أخبرني الآن!
Or I'll kill you right now.
وإلا سأقتلك الآن.
The Imperial Sword isn't in Wujia Village.
السيف الإمبراطوري ليس موجوداً في قرية ووجيا.
Wu Mao!
وو ماو!
Hurry, hurry!
أسرعوا، أسرعوا!
Sir!
سيد!
I saw someone take the sword away.
رأيت أحدهم يأخذ السيف.
What?
ماذا؟
Really.
حقًا.
My men are already heading to the capital.
رجالي يتجهون بالفعل إلى العاصمة.
If I die in Mou County,
إذا متُّ في مقاطعة مو،
you won't escape responsibility.
لن تفلت من المسؤولية.
I'm the only son of the Duke of Nan.
أنا الابن الوحيد لدوق نان.
And a favorite of the emperor.
وكان مفضلاً لدى الإمبراطور.
Liang Qing—
ليانغ تشينغ —
is just a neglected Your Highness.
إنه مجرد أمر مهمل يا صاحب السمو.
Lord Nan,
اللورد نان،
we should think long-term.
ينبغي أن نفكر على المدى البعيد.
So tell me,
أخبرني إذن،
what can I get out of this?
ما الذي يمكنني الحصول عليه من هذا؟
A wise man adapts to the times.
الرجل الحكيم يتكيف مع زمانه.
Talents like Lord Nan
مواهب مثل اللورد نان
in the Shi Family Army
في جيش عائلة شي
could easily be a general.
قد يكون بسهولة جنرالاً.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
General...
عام...
Nan Batian, what are you up to?
نان باتيان، ماذا تفعلين؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
You—
أنت-
Of course, I'm untying you, sir.
بالطبع، سأقوم بفك قيودك يا ​​سيدي.
Sir,
سيد،
Let's keep our agreement.
لنلتزم باتفاقنا.
Lord Nan saved my life.
أنقذ اللورد نان حياتي.
I will keep my word.
سأفي بوعدي.
But—
لكن-
Sir, you tell me—
سيدي، أخبرني أنت—
With Liang Qing here,
مع وجود ليانغ تشينغ هنا،
I can't finish the emperor's task.
لا أستطيع إتمام مهمة الإمبراطور.
I can't get Lord Nan a post.
لا أستطيع أن أجد منشوراً للورد نان.
I might not even survive to return.
قد لا أعيش حتى أعود.
Come.
يأتي.
Sir, this place is too rough.
سيدي، هذا المكان قاسٍ للغاية.
Let's go to my office instead.
لنذهب إلى مكتبي بدلاً من ذلك.
We can discuss things in detail.
يمكننا مناقشة الأمور بالتفصيل.
Sir, please, please.
سيدي، من فضلك، من فضلك.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Slow down, slow down.
خفف السرعة، خفف السرعة.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Sir, slow down.
سيدي، خفف السرعة.
Stop!
قف!
Speak.
يتكلم.
Why are you following us?
لماذا تتابعنا؟
You can see
يمكنك أن ترى
I mean no harm.
لا أقصد أي أذى.
I just want to know
أريد فقط أن أعرف
the truth behind my family's massacre.
الحقيقة وراء مذبحة عائلتي.
Don't worry, Village Chief.
لا تقلق يا رئيس القرية.
I'll deliver it to Lord Shi.
سأسلمها إلى اللورد شي.
Come.
يأتي.
Carry it.
احمله.
Be careful on the road.
كن حذراً على الطريق.
Please take care of Ying'er, Chief.
أرجو منك يا رئيس أن تعتني بـ يينغ إير.
Go back.
عُد.
Safe travels.
رحلة سعيدة.
Chief, will there be any trouble?
يا رئيس، هل ستكون هناك أي مشكلة؟
Our words alone aren't enough.
كلماتنا وحدها لا تكفي.
They'll blame the big families.
سيلقون باللوم على العائلات الكبيرة.
In the end, only the magistrate
في النهاية، القاضي وحده هو من يتدخل
will be charged with mismanagement.
سيتم توجيه تهمة سوء الإدارة إليه.
Instead of waiting for the enemy to slip up,
بدلاً من انتظار العدو ليرتكب خطأً،
we should strike first.
ينبغي أن نبدأ بالهجوم.
Turn their trick against them.
اقلب حيلتهم عليهم.